{
  "students": [
    {
      "username": "mohamed",
      "email": "mohamed@mohamed.com",
      "password": "123",
      "subjects": [
        {
          "name": "math",
          "id": "2",
          "degree": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "german",
          "id": "3",
          "degree": 0
        },
        {
          "name": "حساب",
          "id": "1",
          "degree": 1
        },
        {
          "name": "JavaScript",
          "id": "d981",
          "degree": 1
        }
      ],
      "id": "1"
    },
    {
      "username": "ahmed",
      "email": "ahmed@ahmed.com",
      "password": "123",
      "subjects": [
        {
          "name": "math",
          "id": "2",
          "degree": 2
        }
      ],
      "id": "9"
    },
    {
      "username": "sayed",
      "email": "sayed@sayed.com",
      "password": "123",
      "id": "6"
    },
    {
      "username": "ali",
      "email": "ali@ali.com",
      "password": "123",
      "id": "10"
    },
    {
      "username": "mano",
      "email": "mano@mano.com",
      "password": "123",
      "subjects": [
        {
          "name": "german",
          "id": "3",
          "degree": 1
        }
      ],
      "id": "11"
    }
  ],
  "doctor": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "email": "admin@admin.com",
      "password": "123",
      "id": "1"
    }
  ],
  "subjects": [
    {
      "name": "math",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "2+2",
          "answer1": "4",
          "answer2": "5",
          "answer3": "2",
          "answer4": "8",
          "correctAnswer": "4"
        },
        {
          "question": "2+3",
          "answer1": "4",
          "answer2": "5",
          "answer3": "2",
          "answer4": "8",
          "correctAnswer": "5"
        }
      ],
      "id": "2"
    },
    {
      "name": "Bio",
      "questions": [],
      "id": "4"
    },
    {
      "name": "regt",
      "questions": [],
      "id": "5"
    },
    {
      "name": "gg",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "gdfgd",
          "answer1": "gdd",
          "answer2": "dg",
          "answer3": "dg",
          "answer4": "dg",
          "correctAnswer": "dg"
        }
      ],
      "id": "6"
    },
    {
      "name": "dasf",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "faf",
          "answer1": "sdf",
          "answer2": "a",
          "answer3": "ff",
          "answer4": "ff",
          "correctAnswer": "ff"
        }
      ],
      "id": "7"
    },
    {
      "name": "ew",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "sfa",
          "answer1": "af",
          "answer2": "fa",
          "answer3": "afs",
          "answer4": "asf",
          "correctAnswer": "afs"
        }
      ],
      "id": "8"
    },
    {
      "name": "ggdg",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "gdfbd",
          "answer1": "ag",
          "answer2": "d",
          "answer3": "hff",
          "answer4": "fgd",
          "correctAnswer": "hff"
        }
      ],
      "id": "9"
    },
    {
      "name": "gg",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "dfg",
          "answer1": "df",
          "answer2": "gdf",
          "answer3": "g",
          "answer4": "dd",
          "correctAnswer": "df"
        }
      ],
      "id": "10"
    },
    {
      "name": "dasd",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "dasav",
          "answer1": "asd",
          "answer2": "as",
          "answer3": "sdvvsd",
          "answer4": "A",
          "correctAnswer": "A"
        }
      ],
      "id": "13"
    },
    {
      "name": "fds",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "ssdfgs",
          "answer1": "f",
          "answer2": "afsd",
          "answer3": "sfd",
          "answer4": "sdf",
          "correctAnswer": "afsd"
        }
      ],
      "id": "14"
    },
    {
      "name": "ad",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "fasf",
          "answer1": "sfs",
          "answer2": "dsdsfa",
          "answer3": "afs",
          "answer4": "dasf",
          "correctAnswer": "dasf"
        }
      ],
      "id": "15"
    },
    {
      "name": "ffsd",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "asff",
          "answer1": "afaf",
          "answer2": "asfa",
          "answer3": "afa",
          "answer4": "fasf",
          "correctAnswer": "afaf"
        }
      ],
      "id": "16"
    },
    {
      "name": "dasd",
      "questions": [],
      "id": "17"
    },
    {
      "id": "d981",
      "name": "JavaScript",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "how to read data in the console?",
          "answer1": "Console.log",
          "answer2": "print",
          "answer3": "system.out.print",
          "answer4": "read",
          "correctAnswer": "Console.log"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "login": [
    {
      "username": "ahmed",
      "role": "students",
      "id": "1"
    }
  ]
}